That before the vigilance infection, you have to
take a photo of the meter, that is, the
shoulder which has to be covered from inside,
in the photo there is a point on the chassis and here,
you have to take a photo of the
front side left hand corner photo,
that is the full photo of the
left hand side, in this the
entire vehicle was shown, I
wanted a photo of the real side left hand corner in which all the four lower
tyres should be visible,
you have to take a full photo of the real side,
rear right hand real corner photo,
right hand full photo, and right hand
front side corner in which
you have to take the food of the front side of both the sides,
now your number plate should be visible in the engine compartments,
Ranjan comment, thank you